Guide to the John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0700
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 2000-2013; Accession ARCH-2015-138
  - Fellowships, 10/10/2012 - 6/17/2013; AA 8 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Fulbright Fellowship, 10/12/2011 - 5/3/2013; AA 8_16 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Terman Fellows, 10/17/2008 - 9/11/2012; AA 8_30 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Faculty/Prof. Chairs, 5/14/2008 - 9/29/2010; AA 10 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Stanford Historical Society, 7/15/2010 - 3/10/2011; AD 1_2 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Judicial Affairs, 11/12/2007 - 10/28/2013; AD 3_10 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Hoover House, 6/20/2007 - 5/12/2008; AD 4_7 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - University Cabinet, 11/8/2001 - 5/30/2007; AD 4_13 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, General, 12/16/2011 - 8/22/2013; AD 4_20 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - News Clippings/Editorials, 10/3/2012 - 7/8/2013; AD 4_20_1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 10/3/2012 - 6/6/2013; AD 4_20_3 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Appreciation letters, 9/24/2012 - 8/20/2013; AD 4_20_4_1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Invitations (1 of 4), 9/5/2012 - 10/2/2012; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Invitations (2 of 4), 10/3/2012 - 1/25/2013; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Invitations (3 of 4), 1/29/2013 - 4/16/2013; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Invitations (4 of 4), 4/17/2013 - 8/29/2013; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Holiday Cards, 9/24/2012 - 1/22/2013; AD 4_20_4_4 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Nonsense (1 of 3), 9/17/2012 - 11/9/2012; AD 4_20_5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Nonsense (2 of 3), 12/4/2012 - 2/6/2013; AD 4_20_5 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Nonsense (3 of 3), 2/14/2013 - 8/29/2013; AD 4_20_5 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1/21/2005 - 8/14/2013; AD 4_20_6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations, Students, 12/6/2005 - 10/15/2012; AD 4_20_6_1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Solicitations (1 of 7), 9/4/2012 - 10/29/2012; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Solicitations (2 of 7), 10/31/2012 - 1/15/2013; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Solicitations (3 of 7), 1/16/2013 - 3/25/2013; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Solicitations (4 of 7), 3/27/2013 - 4/29/2013; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Solicitations (5 of 7), 4/30/2013 - 5/17/2013; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Solicitations (6 of 7), 5/20/2013 - 7/24/2013; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Solicitations (7 of 7), 7/25/2013 - 8/27/2013; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - University Communications, 10/5/2012 - 8/29/2013; AD 4_22 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (1 of 2), 9/4/2012 - 1/31/2013; AD 8_1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (2 of 2), 2/1/2013 - 8/27/2013; AD 8_1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Student Affairs, 10/11/2012 - 8/27/2013; AD 8_8 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bing Overseas Studies, 9/14/2012 - 6/14/2013; AD 8_11 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Financial Aid, 9/14/2012 - 4/19/2013; AD 8_12 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Residential Dining Ent., 1/23/2013 - 8/22/2013; AD 8_18_11 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Emploment Inquiries, 9/18/2012 - 8/26/2013; AD 10_1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Lively Arts, 9/21/2012 - 1/23/2013; AD 11_7_5_2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Freshman Issues, 9/5/2012 - 9/5/2012; AD 11_7_7 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Media Publications, Misc., 5/25/2007 - 8/29/2013; AD 11_8 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Surveys, Questionnaires, 12/4/2012 - 7/15/2013; AD 11_8_10 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Media Publications (internal), 5/7/2012 - 7/30/2013; AD 11_8_11 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Administrative Resources, 11/24/2008 - 6/18/2010; AD 12_2_3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Budget Group, 10/3/2012 - 1/31/2013; AD 12_5 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Tuition, 8/3/2009 - 2/20/2013; AD 12_5_4 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Risk Management, 10/26/2012 - 7/25/2013; AD 12_8 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Office of Development, 9/28/2012 - 8/19/2013; AD 12_10_1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hoover House Circle, Founders' Circle, 3/2006 - 10/9/2012; AD 12_10_2_6 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Donor Relations, 11/28/2011 - 7/1/2013; AD 12_10_2_7 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Stanford Challenge, 10/21/2011 - 5/23/2012; AD 12_10_2_8 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Asian Relations, 10/2/2012 - 8/7/2013; AD 12_10_2_9 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Land, Buildings, Real Estate, 8/6/2012 - 10/24/2012; AD 12_14 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 7/26/2012 - 8/22/2013; AD 12_14_7_5 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Church, 8/23/2011 - 8/14/2013; AD 12_14_7_50 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Parking Transportation, 10/31/2011 - 8/6/2013; AD 12_14_7_53 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 12/5/2000 - 8/19/2013; AL 1_3 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 10/16/2012 - 6/13/2013; Al 3 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Alumni giving, general, 9/2/2008 - 6/19/2013; AL 5 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, Board of Trustees, 10/5/2012 - 2/14/2013; B 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 9/21/2011 - 2/6/2013; B 14 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 11/29/2012 - 8/12/2013; C 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - University Committees, 2/16/2010 - 10/8/2012; C 6 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Office of Government and Community Relations, 10/3/2012 - 7/15/2013; G 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - California State Government, 11/20/2012 - 8/28/2013; G 1_2 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - United States Government Relations, 4/15/2011 - 7/9/2013; G 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Defense, Department of, 9/20/2011 - 10/2/2012; G 3_7 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - National Aeronautics Space Administration (NASA), 7/5/2012 - 8/27/2013; G 3_7_4 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - National Institutes of Health, 9/14/2012 - 1/29/2013; G 3_8_2 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 10/23/2012 - 8/15/2013; G 3_8_3 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - National Science Foundation, 9/27/2012 - 6/19/2013; G 3_19 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Foreign Government, 9/28/2012 - 4/1/2013; G 5 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - SHC Administration, 1/12/2012 - 8/27/2013; SHS 3 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute (HHMI), 3/20/2012 - 5/24/2013; SHS 9 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - School of Medicine, 10/12/2005 - 5/3/2013; M 1 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - School of Medicine Dev., 9/21/2006 - 4/5/2007; M 2 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - School of Medicine Departments, Miscellaneous, 12/16/2010 - 7/17/2013; M 5 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Institute for Stem Cell Biology and Regenerative Medicine, 5/28/2008 - 8/27/2013; M 5_1 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous (1 of 3), 12/29/2006 - 11/14/2012; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous (2 of 3), 11/20/2012 - 2/25/2013; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous (3 of 3), 3/19/2013 - 8/28/2013; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Education Groups/Organizations, 5/31/2012 - 8/21/2013; O 3 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 8/8/2012 - 7/24/2013; O 3_1 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Consortium of Social Science Associations (COSSA), 7/24/2000 - 9/9/2009; O 3_3 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - American Academy of Arts Sciences, 9/21/2012 - 8/19/2013; O 3_7 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - American Council on Education, 10/15/2012 - 8/5/2013; O 3_8 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - NAICU, 2/8/2013 - 7/29/2013; O 3_10 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Aspen Institute, 1/7/2013 - 6/19/2013; O 3_37 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - The National Academies, 9/4/2012 - 8/27/2013; O 3_43 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - NCAA, 10/15/2009 - 8/29/2013; O 3_44 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Pacific-12 Conference, 3/26/2012 - 6/3/2013; O 3_47 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Organizations, 12/11/2012 - 8/7/2013; O 4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Korn/Ferry International, 2/6/2006 - 1/4/2012; O 5_1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Universities Colleges (1 of 3), 4/29/2002 - 10/9/2012; O 8 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Universities Colleges (2 of 3), 10/11/2012 - 1/9/2013; O 8 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Universities Colleges (3 of 3), 1/18/2013 - 8/26/2013; O 8 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Universities, 9/16/2009 - 11/29/2012; O 8_7 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University, 2/13/2006 - 6/12/2007; O 8_19 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Harvard University, 3/12/2012 - 8/7/2013; O 8_23 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Princeton University, 10/26/2012 - 3/19/2013; O 8_36 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - University of California, 7/9/2008 - 8/5/2013; O 8_43 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - University of Southern California, 9/20/2012 - 6/17/2013; O 8_49 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Western Association of Schools Colleges (WASC), 1/9/2012 - 8/27/2013; O 8_52 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Inaugurations, 9/4/2012 - 8/27/2013; O 8_55 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 10/9/2012 - 8/20/2013; O 11 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - American Philosophical Society, 10/4/2011 - 7/1/2013; O 15 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Vice Provost and Dean of Research, 10/5/2011 - 8/26/2013; R 0 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Freeman Spogli Institute for International Studies, 1/11/2007 - 4/3/2012; R 1_12 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Woods Institute for the Environment, 5/15/2007 - 12/2/2010; R 4_2_1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Science Coalition, 10/21/2008 - 12/4/2009; R 8 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Students, Miscellaneous, 9/27/2012 - 1/23/2013; ST 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Student Groups, Miscellaneous, 9/23/2011 - 5/24/2013; ST 1_1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - KZSU Student Radio, 10/31/2012 - 8/14/2013; ST 3_18 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Haas Center for Public Service, 1/15/2010 - 11/1/2013; ST 3_29 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Campus Compact, 5/15/2012 - 5/14/2013; ST 3_35 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 7/31/2002 - 3/15/2013; ST 8 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- President's records, 2013-2014; Accession ARCH-2016-116
  - Graduate Education, 12/9/2013 - 6/25/2014; AA 1_13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Education, 9/4/2013 - 8/4/2014; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Continuing Studies, 4/17/2014 - 5/16/2014; AA 3_6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Summer Programs, 6/3/2013 - 8/25/2014; AA 3_16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - School of Humanities Sciences, 9/6/2013 - 8/19/2014; AA 4_1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Art, Dept. of, 1/7/2013 - 11/6/2013; AA 4_1_9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dance, Dept. of, 12/5/2013 - 6/23/2014; AA 4_1_16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Computer Science, Dept. of, 12/31/2013 - 6/4/2014; AA 4_1_17 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - French Italian, Dept. of, 10/13/2006 - 8/21/2014; AA 4_1_22 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Department of Athletics, 10/14/2013 - 8/25/2014; AA 4_1_30 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Football Games, Rose Bowl, 9/19/2013 - 8/11/2014; AA 4_1_30_1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - GSB, 11/5/2013 - 8/13/2014; AA 4_2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Engineering, School of, 9/27/2013 - 6/23/2014; AA 4_4 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Education, School of, 9/26/2013 - 7/2/2014; AA 4_5 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Hoover Institution, 9/26/2013 - 8/28/2014; AA 4_9 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Stanford University Libraries, 10/24/2013 - 8/28/2014; AA 4_12 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Law School, 12/10/2013 - 8/27/2014; AA 4_15 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Awards Prizes (1 of 2), 9/3/2013 - 12/31/2013; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Awards Prizes (2 of 2), 1/29/2014 - 8/25/2014; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Grants Scholarships, 8/26/2013 - 8/28/2014; AA 6 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fellowships, 9/19/2013 - 5/5/2014; AA 8 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Fulbright Fellowship, 9/19/2013 - 7/8/2014; AA 8_16 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 6/6/2013 - 5/23/2014; AA 8_25 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Judicial Affairs, 11/6/2013 - 6/30/2014; AD 3_10 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, General, 9/26/2013 - 8/28/2014; AD 4_20 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings/Editorials, 10/17/2013 - 6/2/2014; AD 4_20_1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 10/22/2013 - 8/20/2014; AD 4_20_3 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Appreciation letters, 9/6/2013 - 8/28/2014; AD 4_20_4_1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Invitations (1 of 3), 9/3/2013 - 12/31/2013; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Invitations (2 of 3), 1/1/2014 - 3/28/2014; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Invitations (3 of 3), 4/2/2014 - 8/25/2014; AD 4_20_4_2 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Holiday Cards, 9/26/2013 - 1/28/2014; AD 4_20_4_4 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Nonsense (1 of 3), 9/13/2013 - 2/26/2014; AD 4_20_5 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Nonsense (2 of 3), 3/4/2014 - 6/26/2014; AD 4_20_5 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Nonsense (3 of 3), 6/30/2014 - 8/28/2014; AD 4_20_5 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Recommendation Letters, 2/20/2014 - 8/25/2014; AD 4_20_6 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Solicitations (1 of 7), 9/3/2013 - 10/31/2013; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Solicitations (2 of 7), 11/1/2013 - 12/31/2013; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Solicitations (3 of 7), 1/1/2014 - 2/28/2014; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Solicitations (4 of 7), 3/4/2014 - 3/31/2014; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Solicitations (5 of 7), 4/1/2014 - 4/29/2014; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Solicitations (6 of 7), 5/1/2014 - 6/30/2014; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Solicitations (7 of 7), 7/8/2014 - 8/28/2014; AD 4_20_8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - University Communications, 9/9/2013 - 6/26/2014; AD 4_22 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (1 of 3), 9/5/2013 - 2/28/2014; AD 8_1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (2 of 3), 3/3/2014 - 4/28/2014; AD 8_1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Admissions (3 of 3), 5/1/2014 - 8/27/2014; AD 8_1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Student Affairs, 10/17/2013 - 7/30/2014; AD 8_8 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Emploment Inquiries, 9/5/2013 - 8/25/2014; AD 10_1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lively Arts, 9/5/2013 - 12/31/2013; AD 11_7_5_2 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Media Publications, Misc., 9/3/2013 - 8/25/2014; AD 11_8 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Surveys, Questionnaires, 4/24/2014 - 8/25/2014; AD 11_8_10 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Media Publications (internal), 3/11/2014 - 6/27/2014; AD 11_8_11 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Business Affairs, CFO, 6/20/2014 - 8/18/2014; AD 12_2 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Risk Management, 10/25/2013 - 8/18/2014; AD 12_8 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Office of Development, 9/3/2013 - 8/20/2014; AD 12_10_1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Stanford Fund, 10/9/2012 - 9/24/2013; AD 12_10_2_3 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Asian Relations, 10/17/2013 - 6/6/2014; AD 12_10_2_9 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Memorial Church, 2/28/2014 - 8/27/2014; AD 12_14_7_50 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Conferences, Misc., 1/17/2013 - 8/20/2014; AD 13_10_1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Relations, 10/8/2012 - 4/14/2014; AL 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 8/15/2013 - 8/28/2014; AL 1_3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Events, 9/26/2012 - 4/17/2014; AL 1_7 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 9/26/2013 - 5/29/2014; AL 3 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Board of Trustees, 2/18/2014 - 4/25/2014; B 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 5/9/2014 - 7/21/2014; B 14 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Office of Government and Community Relations, 10/3/2013 - 6/30/2014; G 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - California State Government, 2/24/2014 - 6/2/2014; G 1_2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - United States Government Relations, 9/16/2013 - 7/23/2014; G 3 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Energy, Department of, 10/21/2011 - 12/10/2013; G 3_7_2 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 10/30/2013 - 8/18/2014; G 3_8_3 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation, 10/31/2013 - 8/14/2014; G 3_19 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Local Government, 12/19/2012 - 3/31/2014; G 4 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Government, 10/17/2013 - 7/28/2014; G 5 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - School of Medicine, 11/1/2013 - 8/25/2014; M 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - School of Medicine Departments, Miscellaneous, 10/9/2013 - 8/28/2014; M 5 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous (1 of 3), 6/10/2013 - 11/27/2013; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous (2 of 3), 12/4/2013 - 4/28/2014; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous (3 of 3), 5/5/2014 - 8/25/2014; O 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Education Groups/Organizations, 9/17/2013 - 8/18/2014; O 3 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 1/17/2013 - 8/5/2014; O 3_1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - APRU, 9/17/2008 - 6/12/2014; O 3_4 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - American Academy of Arts Sciences, 6/11/2002 - 12/16/2013; O 3_7 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - American Council on Education, 9/19/2013 - 8/28/2014; O 3_8 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - NAICU, 9/24/2013 - 7/23/2014; O 3_10 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The College Board, 3/27/2012 - 2/19/2014; O 3_25 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Aspen Institute, 11/4/2013 - 2/24/2014; O 3_37 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - The National Academies, 9/11/2013 - 8/13/2014; O 3_43 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - NCAA, 9/4/2013 - 7/29/2014; O 3_44 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Pacific-12 Conference, 9/19/2013 - 6/30/2014; O 3_47 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Research Organizations, Misc., 11/1/2013 - 8/20/2014; O 7 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Universities Colleges (1 of 2), 2/4/2002 - 3/12/2014; O 8 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Universities Colleges (2 of 2), 4/7/2014 - 8/25/2014; O 8 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Association of Independent CA Colleges and Universities (AICCU), 1/14/2014 - 7/30/2014; O 8_9 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Caltech, 7/9/2012 - 2/13/2014; O 8_16 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Peking University, 10/18/2013 - 6/30/2014; O 8_30 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - University of California, 9/20/2013 - 4/14/2014; O 8_43 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - University of Southern California, 11/21/2013 - 8/12/2014; O 8_49 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Inaugurations, 9/3/2013 - 8/27/2014; O 8_55 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 12/18/2013 - 8/7/2014; O 11 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - California Council on Science and Technology (CCST), 7/12/2012 - 12/16/2013; O 12 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - American Philosophical Society, 9/11/2013 - 6/30/2014; O 15 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Institute for Gender Research, 12/9/2013 - 5/6/2014; R 1_8 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Improving K-12 Education, 6/5/2007 - 12/19/2013; R 4_4 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Students, Miscellaneous, 9/24/2013 - 8/18/2014; ST 1 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Student Groups, Miscellaneous, 10/17/2013 - 6/27/2014; ST 1_1 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU), 3/28/2013 - 5/29/2014; ST 2 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 12/3/2013 - 8/20/2014; ST 8 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- President's records, 2000 Sep 1-2016 Aug 31; Accession ARCH-2016-117
  - 9/5/2000 - 9/29/2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 9/7/2000 - 9/29/2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 10/5/2000 - 10/31/2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 10/2/2000 - 10/31/2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 11/9/2000 - 11/30/2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 11/1/2000 - 11/29/2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 12/7/2000 - 12/21/2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 12/4/2000 - 12/22/2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1/1/2001 - 1/26/2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1/3/2001 - 1/26/2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2/2/2001 - 2/20/2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2/2/2001 - 2/27/2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 3/1/2001 - 3/30/2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 3/1/2001 - 3/28/2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 4/2/2001 - 4/30/2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 4/3/2001 - 4/30/2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 5/2/2001 - 5/31/2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 5/1/2001 - 5/31/2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 6/1/2001 - 6/29/2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 6/1/2001 - 6/29/2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 7/6/2001 - 7/31/2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 7/9/2001 - 7/31/2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 8/1/2001 - 8/31/2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 8/1/2001 - 8/31/2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 9/1/2001 - 9/30/2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 9/5/2001 - 9/27/2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 10/1/2001 - 10/30/2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 10/1/2001 - 10/31/2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 11/1/2001 - 11/28/2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 11/1/2001 - 11/21/2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 12/4/2001 - 12/21/2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 12/3/2001 - 12/21/2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1/2/ 2002 - 1/29/ 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1/2/ 2002 - 1/31/ 2002 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 2/4/ 2002 - 2/27/ 2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 2/1/ 2002 - 2/28/ 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 3/1/ 2002 - 3/28/ 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 3/4/ 2002 - 3/21/ 2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 4/1/ 2002 - 4/30/ 2002 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 4/1/ 2002 - 4/30/ 2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 5/1/ 2002 - 5/31/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 5/1/ 2002 - 5/31/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 6/4/ 2002 - 6/27/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 6/4/ 2002 - 6/28/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 7/2/ 2002 - 7/30/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 7/1/ 2002 - 7/24/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 8/9/ 2002 - 8/29/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 8/13/ 2002 - 8/30/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 9/1/ 2002 - 9/30/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 9/4/ 2002 - 9/30/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 10/1/ 2002 - 10/30/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 10/1/ 2002 - 10/25/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 11/1/ 2002 - 11/26/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 11/4/ 2002 - 11/26/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 12/4/ 2002 - 12/20/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 12/4/ 2002 - 12/20/ 2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1/2/2003 - 1/31/2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 1/7/2003 - 1/29/2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 2/3/2003 - 2/27/2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 2/3/2003 - 2/28/2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 3/5/2003 - 3/31/2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 3/5/2003 - 3/31/2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 4/1/2003 - 4/30/2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 4/1/2003 - 4/30/2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 5/1/2003 - 5/30/2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 5/1/2003 - 5/30/2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 6/4/2003 - 6/26/2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 6/2/2003 - 6/20/2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 7/3/2003 - 7/31/2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 7/7/2003 - 7/31/2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 8/4/2003 - 8/28/2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 8/1/2003 - 8/22/2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 9/1/2003 - 9/30/2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 9/2/2003 - 9/29/2003 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 10/1/2003 - 10/28/2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 10/2/2003 - 10/29/2003 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 11/6/2003 - 11/26/2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 11/5/2003 - 11/25/2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 12/1/2003 - 12/20/2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 12/2/2003 - 12/19/2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 1/4/2004 - 1/27/2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1/5/2004 - 1/30/2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 2/2/2004 - 2/25/2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 2/2/2004 - 2/27/2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 3/1/2004 - 3/26/2004 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 3/1/2004 - 3/26/2004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 4/2/2004 - 4/30/2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 4/1/2004 - 4/30/2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 5/1/2004 - 5/21/2004 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 5/3/2004 - 5/19/2004 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 6/1/2004 - 6/25/2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 6/1/2004 - 6/25/2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 7/6/2004 - 7/28/2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 7/6/2004 - 7/29/2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 8/4/2004 - 8/27/2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 8/2/2004 - 8/27/2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 9/15/2004 - 9/30/2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 9/16/2004 - 9/24/2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 10/4/2004 - 10/28/2004 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 10/1/2004 - 10/29/2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 11/1/2004 - 11/24/2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 11/2/2004 - 11/24/2004 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 12/8/2004 - 12/31/2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 12/8/2004 - 12/16/2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1/2/2005 - 1/31/2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1/3/2005 - 1/31/2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 2/1/2005 - 2/28/2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 2/1/2005 - 2/28/2005 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 3/1/2005 - 3/31/2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 3/1/2005 - 3/31/2005 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 4/1/2005 - 4/28/2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 4/1/2005 - 4/27/2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 5/2/2005 - 5/27/2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 5/2/2005 - 5/27/2005 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 6/1/2005 - 6/30/2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 6/1/2005 - 6/30/2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 7/1/2005 - 7/29/2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 7/1/2005 - 7/29/2005 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 8/1/2005 - 8/30/2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 8/1/2005 - 8/29/2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 9/12/2005 - 9/29/2005 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 9/13/2005 - 9/30/2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 10/1/2005 - 10/31/2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 10/4/2005 - 10/28/2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 11/1/2005 - 11/28/2005 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 11/1/2005 - 11/21/2005 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 12/1/2005 - 12/15/2005 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 12/14/2005 - 12/16/2005 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1/3/2006 - 1/31/2006 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1/3/2006 - 1/31/2006 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 2/2/2006 - 2/28/2006 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 2/1/2006 - 2/28/2006 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 3/1/2006 - 3/22/2006 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 3/1/2006 - 3/28/2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 4/3/2006 - 4/28/2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)